MAKINDE OLUWASEGUN CHUKWUEMEKA

Permanent Address: No.1 Annams Close, Chinedu Street, Location Road, Oyigbo, Rivers State. **Mobile:** (+234)8161805190. Email: Shegeemankinde@gmail.com **LinkedIn**: makinde oluwasegun

Personal Profile Summary

Dedicated Mechanical Engineer with good knowledge in inspection and maintenance of mechanical equipments and automobiles. Production planning and management engineer with excellent marketing strategy and planning. Computer literate with ten years experience in Microsoft Office and engineering softwares.

Education

University of Port Harcourt

October 2013 – September 2018

Port Harcourt, Rivers State.

Bachelor of Engineering in Mechanical Engineering.

CGPA| 64.05%

Trainings And Certification

Alison

Introduction To Production Planning And Control – 90% Production And Operations Management -85% Manufacturing Process -87%

November, 2021 December, 2021 December, 2021

Work Experience

Benz Affairs Limited

June 2017- December 2021

Battery Technician

- Assembled, installed, inspected, and maintained batteries in Benz Vehicles.
- Repaired and recharged batteries for all electric- operated warehouse equipment.
- Removed and replaced battery connectors and contact tips.
- Operated transfer carts to change batteries in and out of equipment while maintaining proper rotation of batteries.

Mechanical Technician

- Sales of vehicle parts to customers
- Inspected vehicle engine repair and vehicle components.
- Diagnosis of Mercedes Benz vehicles using engine diagnostic pad.
- Repaired, upgraded and maintained vehicle systems.
- Maintained and installed automobile electrical/electronic components.
- Mechanical maintenance report writing.

National Youth Service Corps (NYSC)

November 2019 - November 2020

Community Secondary School, Senior Ikodi-engenni, Ahoada West

Science Teacher

- Teaching in Physics, Mathematics
- Community Development Services

Software's Skills

- Microsoft office proficient (10 years)
- Solidworks (5 years)
- JavaScript programming

Leadership Positions and Volunteering

Divine Mercy Seat Assembly

Assistance Youth Pastor

August 2014- June 2019

Achievement: Introduced a Skill development group which certified more than fifty youths.

Divine Mercy Seat Assembly

Lead Pastor June 2019- Present

Achievement: Restructured accounting system and leadership position, built a club for children development with fifty children benefiting and scholarship for five children.

REFEREES:

Bishop Jonathan Alao Duolus Christian Church Port Harcourt, Rivers State 08037205594

Mr. Henry Afuwowe. NETCODIETSMANN Station Chemist +234(0)8037049849.